[
    {"question": "low-key", "answer": "控えめな、秘密な"},
    {"question": "sloppy", "answer": "雑な"},
    {"question": "black and white", "answer": "明らかな、白黒はっきりしている"},
    {"question": "drive sb up the wall", "answer": "〜をイライラさせる"},
    {"question": "kick sb out", "answer": "〜を追い出す"},
    {"question": "over the top", "answer": "やり過ぎの、行き過ぎの"},
    {"question": "ancient", "answer": "めちゃくちゃ古い"},
    {"question": "watch out for sth/sb", "answer": "〜に気をつける"},
    {"question": "figure sth out", "answer": "〜を理解する"},
    {"question": "slack off", "answer": "ダラダラする"},
    {"question": "overpaid", "answer": "（お金を）もらいすぎの"},
    {"question": "better off", "answer": "（〜の）方が良い"},
    {"question": "grab sth", "answer": "(ご飯や飲み物を）買う"},
    {"question": "take sth out of context", "answer": "文脈を無視して〜を解釈する"},
    {"question": "freebie", "answer": "無料でもらったもの"},
    {"question": "clear-cut", "answer": "（考えや行動が）明確な"},
    {"question": "cut sb off", "answer": "（会話などの途中で）〜を遮る"},
    {"question": "gray area", "answer": "微妙、グレーゾーン"},
    {"question": "fiddly", "answer": "面倒くさい、厄介な"},
    {"question": "crystal-clear", "answer": "とても明確な、明らかな"},

    {"question": "downtime", "answer": "忙しくない時期、ゆっくりした時間"},
    {"question": "check sth out", "answer": "〜を確認する、試しに行ってみる"},
    {"question": "get it", "answer": "理解する"},
    {"question": "hold sth/sb up", "answer": "〜を遅らせる、時間を取らせる"},
    {"question": "legit", "answer": "ちゃんとした"},
    {"question": "catch up", "answer": "（久しぶりに）会う"},
    {"question": "hyped", "answer": "ワクワクした"},
    {"question": "attention-seeking", "answer": "注目されたがる、かまってちゃんの"},
    {"question": "gonna do", "answer": "（自分の意図を示して）〜する"},
    {"question": "get into sth", "answer": "〜にハマる"},
    {"question": "have butterflies in one's stomach", "answer": "（心配や不安で）ドキドキする"},
    {"question": "cutconers", "answer": "手を抜く"},
    {"question": "pretty much", "answer": "大体、ほぼ"},
    {"question": "big deal", "answer": "大変重要なこと、大きな問題"},
    {"question": "get the ball rolling", "answer": "（物事を）始める"},
    {"question": "spot sth/sb", "answer": "〜を見つける"},
    {"question": "on the dot", "answer": "（数字が）ぴったり、ちょうど"},
    {"question": "bring sth up", "answer": "〜を話に出す、言い出す"},
    {"question": "pricey", "answer": "（値段）が高い"},
    {"question": "touchy subject", "answer": "タブーな話、触れられたくない話"},

    {"question": "one-off", "answer": "一度限りの"},
    {"question": "bug sb", "answer": "〜を邪魔する"},
    {"question": "rusty", "answer": "下手になった"},
    {"question": "bright and early", "answer": "朝早く"},
    {"question": "give sb a buzz", "answer": "〜に電話する"},
    {"question": "work on sth", "answer": "〜を改善する"},
    {"question": "in-your-face", "answer": "攻撃的な；大胆な"},
    {"question": "come clean", "answer": "正直に言う"},
    {"question": "downer", "answer": "がっかりなもの、がっかりした人"},
    {"question": "packed", "answer": "いっぱいの、混んだ"},
    {"question": "bail sb out", "answer": "（困難から）〜を助ける"},
    {"question": "get my head around", "answer": "〜を理解する"},
    {"question": "cut to the chase", "answer": "要点を言う、本題に入る"},
    {"question": "flag sth", "answer": "〜を知らせる"},
    {"question": "old school", "answer": "懐かしい"},
    {"question": "get one's hopes up", "answer": "期待する"},
    {"question": "behind sb's back", "answer": "〜の知らないところで、隠れて"},
    {"question": "get back to sb", "answer": "〜にまた連絡する"},
    {"question": "freak (sb) out", "answer": "〜を驚かす；パニックになる"},
    {"question": "put sth together", "answer": "〜をまとめる、組み立てる"},

    {"question": "sounds like a plan", "answer": "〜で決まり、それでいこう"},
    {"question": "drop sth/sb off", "answer": "〜を送る"},
    {"question": "attention to getail", "answer": "細かいことに気を配れる能力"},
    {"question": "sick of", "answer": "（〜に）飽きた、うんざりした"},
    {"question": "white noise", "answer": "雑音、余計なもの"},
    {"question": "tricky", "answer": "難しい、厄介な"},
    {"question": "slammed", "answer": "とても忙しい"},
    {"question": "in a rush", "answer": "急いでいる"},
    {"question": "nice-to-have", "answer": "あるに越した事はないもの"},
    {"question": "tell me about it", "answer": "（同意を表して）本当だよね"},
    {"question": "take it easy", "answer": "リラックスする、気楽に行く"},
    {"question": "wing it", "answer": "適当に決める、即興でやる"},
    {"question": "turn sth/sb down", "answer": "（オファーを受けて）〜を断る"},
    {"question": "keep one's cool", "answer": "冷静でいる"},
    {"question": "sort of/kind of", "answer": "まぁまぁ、っぽい"},
    {"question": "fill in for sb", "answer": "〜の代わりをする"},
    {"question": "help sb out", "answer": "〜を助ける、手伝う"},
    {"question": "make sure (that)", "answer": "必ず〜するようにする、確かめる"},
    {"question": "keep one's voice down", "answer": "静かにする"},
    {"question": "FYI", "answer": "一応知らせておくけど、参考までに"},

    {"question": "chill", "answer": "ゆるい"},
    {"question": "bite the bullet", "answer": "（我慢して）思い切る"},
    {"question": "look foward to sth", "answer": "〜を楽しみにする"},
    {"question": "on the same page", "answer": "考えや理解が一致している"},
    {"question": "clear sth up", "answer": "〜を明確にする、説明する"},
    {"question": "shattered", "answer": "とてもがっかりした、とても残念な"},
    {"question": "give credit", "answer": "（功績を）褒める"},
    {"question": "close enough", "answer": "良い線いってる、そんなもんだ"},
    {"question": "lock sth down", "answer": "〜を確定する、完成する"},
    {"question": "deal-breaker", "answer": "別れる原因；交渉決裂の要因"},
    {"question": "loaded", "answer": "儲かっている"},
    {"question": "double-check sth/(that)", "answer": "〜を再確認する"},
    {"question": "cutting-edge", "answer": "最先端の、最近の"},
    {"question": "go in circles", "answer": "堂々巡りする、同じことを繰り返す"},
    {"question": "chill out", "answer": "冷静になる；リラックスする"},
    {"question": "break for lunch", "answer": "昼ごはんにする、昼休憩に行く"},
    {"question": "roughly", "answer": "大体、ざっくり言うと"},
    {"question": "stretch", "answer": "無理があること"},
    {"question": "on the right track", "answer": "順調に進んでいる"},
    {"question": "get one's hands on sth", "answer": "〜を手に入れる"}
]
